<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Game Development on Esau's Page</title><link>/categories/game-development/</link><description>Recent content in Game Development on Esau's Page</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/game-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Game Development Club Tutorial: Top Down Shooter</title><link>/p/game-development-club-tutorial-top-down-shooter/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/p/game-development-club-tutorial-top-down-shooter/</guid><description>Welcome! Welcome to the top down shooter tutorial! The purpose of this blog is to be used to follow along during the game development club tutorial meeting but all are welcome to view this and learn from it!
Getting Started Downloading Unity If you don&amp;rsquo;t already have Unity downloaded, go ahead and download the hub
Hub Finishing signing in and navigate to the editor installation area
Editor This tutorial will be using version 2021.</description></item><item><title>My Unreal Adventure! Blog 1: Unreal Engine Intro</title><link>/p/my-unreal-adventure-blog-1-unreal-engine-intro/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/p/my-unreal-adventure-blog-1-unreal-engine-intro/</guid><description>Ever heard of Unreal Engine?
Image of Unreal Engine Logo Image from Unreal Engine 5 Teaser Quick Explanation of Unreal Unreal Engine is a 3D creation tool that primarily enables game developers to create 3D envionrments and experiences. In there own definition:
Free to download, Unreal Engine comes with everything you need to build and ship successful multi-platform games and location-based entertainment for any genre. With full access to source code, a robust C++ API, and Blueprint visual scripting at your fingertips, you can develop your title any way you like.</description></item></channel></rss>